[
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "insects", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "earthquakes", 
      "past cultures through the analysis of material remains", 
      "the study and the art of bell ringing", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "study of horses"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Entomology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stainless Steel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aluminium", 
      "Einsteinium", 
      "Cast Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which metal was invented by British metallurgist Harold Brearley in 1912?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "periodic biological phenomena such as flowering, migration, breeding, etc", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "non-terrestrial life", 
      "religion", 
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "prehistoric life", 
      "the study and analysis of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "study of refuse and trash", 
      "rocks"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phenology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shrew", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rat", 
      "Squirrel", 
      "Beaver"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Rodent Has Given It's Name To A Mean Spirited Or Bad Tempered Woman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "hair and scalp", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "angels", 
      "the ecology of plant communities", 
      "sleep", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "China", 
      "plants; botany", 
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Trichology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shrew", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rat", 
      "Squirrel", 
      "Beaver"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Rodent Has Given It's Name To A Mean Spirited Or Bad Tempered Woman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study or exploration of caves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "methods", 
      "methods", 
      "mechanical, physical, and biochemical functions of living organisms", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
      "glaciers", 
      "cancer", 
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Speleology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Electroconvulsive Therapy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Endrine Cardio Therapy", 
      "Endless Carotid Tears", 
      "Environmental Combined Theatre"
    ], 
    "question": "What Does E C T Stand For", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "one of two main branches of soil science", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wood", 
      "Unidentified flying object phenomena", 
      "microorganisms", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "blackberries", 
      "blood", 
      "waves or wave motions", 
      "the Shroud of Turin"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Pedology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Campanulate", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clochical", 
      "Cambarn", 
      "Belieux"
    ], 
    "question": "What Word Is Used To Describe Bell Shaped Flowers?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "measurement", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations", 
      "spiders and their kind", 
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "the Soviet Union", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "mollusks"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Metrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aminiotic Fluid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Birth Fluid", 
      "Placental Fluid", 
      "Grow Juice"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Fluid Which Surrounds A Foetus Known As?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "blackberries", 
      "grasses", 
      "pollen", 
      "bacteria", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "karyotypes", 
      "everything", 
      "hearing; a branch of medicine"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hieroglyphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Americium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Merylium", 
      "Amon", 
      "Amortis"
    ], 
    "question": "What does the symbol 'Am' represent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a set of words and/or phrases, usually in relation to some particular canon or field of study", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "nematodes", 
      "the nose and its diseases", 
      "parasitic worms", 
      "museum management", 
      "nematodes", 
      "origin of life", 
      "bees", 
      "victims of crime, often applied to characterizing the criminal"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Terminology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Virgil Grissom ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yuri Gagarin", 
      "Alan Shepard", 
      "Neil Armstrong"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the first man to go to space twice?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "water", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "human beings killing other human beings", 
      "wonders, or monsters", 
      "heat", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "viruses", 
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "the Soviet Union"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hydrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Albatross", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bald Eagle", 
      "Perigrine Falcon", 
      "Ostrich"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Bird Has The Largest Wingspan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "birds", 
      "Unidentified flying object phenomena", 
      "the Sumerians", 
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "oceans", 
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "plant diseases", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Archaeozoology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tongue", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "platysma", 
      "buccinator", 
      "epicranius"
    ], 
    "question": "What muscle is joined by the lingual nerve to the brain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the nature and origins of knowledge", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "classification", 
      "victims of crime, often applied to characterizing the criminal", 
      "the climate", 
      "symptoms", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits", 
      "the historical study of languages", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Epistemology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Philips", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Panasonic", 
      "Viewsonic", 
      "Sony"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Dutch Company Began Marketing Compact Disc Players In 1982?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "bees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "animals that may or may not be mythical", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "methods", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "fungi", 
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "myths"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Apiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oxygen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hydrogen", 
      "Dark Matter", 
      "Higgs Bosons"
    ], 
    "question": "Of what is 98% of the weight of water made?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "crime", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "human growth", 
      "spiders and their kind", 
      "blood serum", 
      "blackberries", 
      "society", 
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures", 
      "oceans", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Criminology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tongue", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Heart", 
      "Biceps", 
      "Deltoids"
    ], 
    "question": "What organ is joined to the hyoid bone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a subsection of anatomy that studies the soft parts", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract", 
      "cancer", 
      "ends or final causes", 
      "museum management", 
      "childbirth, sometimes spelled", 
      "men", 
      "study of horses"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Sarcology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Opossum", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel", 
      "Coyote", 
      "Otter"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the only native North American marsupial?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "puzzles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "disease classification", 
      "life in outer space", 
      "medicine relating to women, or of women in general", 
      "the ecology of any individual species", 
      "the ecological interrelationships among communities of organisms", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "birds", 
      "vocal sounds"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Enigmatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Larva", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bulba", 
      "Curla", 
      "Meta"
    ], 
    "question": "The four stages in the lifecycle of an insect are: egg, adult, pupa, and ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "embryos", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the derivation of a persons character traits, by studying the shape of their skull", 
      "ants", 
      "spiders and their kind", 
      "mechanical, physical, and biochemical functions of living organisms", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "the heart", 
      "ligaments", 
      "the study, especially statistical, of elections"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Embryology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Universal Serial Bus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Undivided Special Breaker", 
      "Unilateral Series Buoy", 
      "Unitary System Bar"
    ], 
    "question": "In Computing, What Does The Abbreviation USB Stand for", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the effects of radiation upon living organisms", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fossils of ancient life", 
      "the art and career of using cosmetics to improve beauty", 
      "though not an -ology, is a commemoration of a person's life at his/her funeral", 
      "underground water", 
      "internal secretory glands", 
      "flow", 
      "ticks and mites"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Actinobiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "81", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "14", 
      "12", 
      "26"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the atomic number for thalium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "ants", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wine and winemaking", 
      "water", 
      "algae", 
      "drugs", 
      "a branch of geology that studies sediments", 
      "lightning", 
      "animal diseases", 
      "puzzles"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Formicology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sclera", 
      "Cornea", 
      "Retina"
    ], 
    "question": "Which membrane controls the amount of light entering the eye?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "minerals", 
      "venereal diseases", 
      "disease classification", 
      "water", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "lightning", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dendrochronology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rattlesnakes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spiders", 
      "Frogs", 
      "Beetles"
    ], 
    "question": "__________ gather in groups to sleep through the winter. ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "in ethics, duty", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "the characteristics of the skull", 
      "blackberries", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "windmills, watermills and animal engines", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Deontology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eyes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lips", 
      "Heart", 
      "Brain"
    ], 
    "question": "On what part of the body is an 'LTK procedure' performed?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a parody of astrology", 
      "fungi", 
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "sleep", 
      "viruses", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "the ecology of any individual species"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phenomenology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Grist", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Havok", 
      "Dazzle", 
      "Murmur"
    ], 
    "question": "A group of bees can be called either a hive, a swarm, or a __________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "in ethics, duty", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "the characteristics of the skull", 
      "blackberries", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "windmills, watermills and animal engines", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Deontology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Seismologist", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Geologist", 
      "Barologist", 
      "Gerologist"
    ], 
    "question": "What Do You Call A Person Who Studies Earthquakes?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "algae", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "study of horses", 
      "the phylum Bryozoa", 
      "illness", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phycology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dolphin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Turtle", 
      "Lion", 
      "Gorilla"
    ], 
    "question": "Apart From Humans There Is Only One Other Creature That Has Sex For Pleasure. What is it? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "cells", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "genetic differences in relation to the environment", 
      "war in an interdisciplinary context", 
      "hair and scalp", 
      "lightning", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "the study and design of machines at the molecular level"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cytology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lactic acid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Amenic Acid", 
      "Stomach Acid", 
      "Pectic Acid"
    ], 
    "question": "What chemical compound causes pain in muscles after exercise?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the atmosphere", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "same as Aetiology", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "the therapeutic use of plants", 
      "the Islam", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "the relationship of organisms to each other and to their environment", 
      "religion"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Aerology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Earwig", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ant", 
      "Praying Mantis", 
      "Woodlouse"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Insect Has A Pair Of Prominent Pincers At The Tip Of It's Abdomen?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the field of medicine that deals with the skin", 
      "symptoms", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment", 
      "the study and the art of bell ringing", 
      "sleep, also: hypnology", 
      "weather", 
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "gross and disgusting things"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ecclesiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Seismologist", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Geologist", 
      "Barologist", 
      "Gerologist"
    ], 
    "question": "What Do You Call A Person Who Studies Earthquakes?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "fish", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "oceans", 
      "the Islam", 
      "the field of dermatological anatomical pathology", 
      "animal diseases", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "the nose and its diseases", 
      "the writings and practices of historians"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ichthyology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Polaris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yamaha", 
      "Sirius", 
      "Canis Majoris"
    ], 
    "question": "As what is the North Star also known?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "enzymes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "ticks and mites", 
      "Unidentified flying object phenomena", 
      "classification", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "a synonym of Pulmonology", 
      "the ear and throat; a branch of medicine", 
      "the liver; a branch of medicine", 
      "gross and disgusting things"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Enzymology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hardness", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thickness", 
      "Conductivity", 
      "Resistance"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Moh's Scale A Measure Of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "numbers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system", 
      "the hind regions (rectum, anus, colon and pelvic floor) of the body", 
      "present-day landforms, traditionally on Earth but with increasing frequency on nearby planetary objects", 
      "the hind regions (rectum, anus, colon and pelvic floor) of the body", 
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth", 
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Numerology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Universal Serial Bus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Undivided Special Breaker", 
      "Unilateral Series Buoy", 
      "Unitary System Bar"
    ], 
    "question": "In Computing, What Does The Abbreviation USB Stand for", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "numbers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system", 
      "the hind regions (rectum, anus, colon and pelvic floor) of the body", 
      "present-day landforms, traditionally on Earth but with increasing frequency on nearby planetary objects", 
      "the hind regions (rectum, anus, colon and pelvic floor) of the body", 
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth", 
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Numerology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cats Eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Traffic Light", 
      "Airbag", 
      "Crumple Zone"
    ], 
    "question": "What Road Safety Device Was Invented By Percy Shaw In 1943? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "waves or wave motions", 
      "eggs", 
      "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Scientology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Algae", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Prawns", 
      "Dye", 
      "Sunlight"
    ], 
    "question": "Flamingos are not naturally pink. They get their color from ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "mollusks", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the Earth", 
      "dialects", 
      "religion", 
      "the ecology of any individual species", 
      "the effect of light on chemicals", 
      "humans", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
      "proper names"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Malacology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2", 
      "3", 
      "1"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Chambers Are There In Your Heart?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "algae", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "study of human characteristics", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "minerals", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "the liver; a branch of medicine", 
      "animals"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Algology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tomato", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Garlic", 
      "Onion", 
      "Chili Pepper"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Alicante A Variety Of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "existence", 
      "ticks and mites", 
      "sleep, also: hypnology", 
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "study of human characteristics", 
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Aerobiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Polar Bear", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Grizzly Bear", 
      "Black Bear", 
      "Panda Bear"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Is The Largest Land Carnivore?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "enzymes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "ticks and mites", 
      "Unidentified flying object phenomena", 
      "classification", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "a synonym of Pulmonology", 
      "the ear and throat; a branch of medicine", 
      "the liver; a branch of medicine", 
      "gross and disgusting things"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Enzymology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cp", 
      "Cm", 
      "Co"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the symbol for copper?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "mountains and their mapping", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "cats", 
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
      "genetic differences in relation to the environment", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "a neologism for the Pilates method, a system of physical exercise", 
      "nerves", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Orology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stainless Steel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aluminium", 
      "Einsteinium", 
      "Cast Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which metal was invented by British metallurgist Harold Brearley in 1912?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "things of which we are by nature ignorant, or of things which cannot be known", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "nerves", 
      "algae", 
      "puzzles", 
      "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
      "the causes and treatment of allergies; a branch of medicine", 
      "medicine relating to women, or of women in general", 
      "symptoms"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Agnoiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Seat Belt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cat Eye", 
      "Airbag", 
      "Crumple Zone"
    ], 
    "question": "What Vehicular Safety Device Was First Pantented By Ej Claghorn?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the future", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "flow", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "drugs", 
      "museum management", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "a branch of geology that studies sediments", 
      "ticks and mites", 
      "gross and disgusting things"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Futurology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "J Robert Oppenheimer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Albert Einstein", 
      "Richard Feynman", 
      "Niels Bohr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Director Of The Atomic Lab At Los Alamos New Mexico?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "study of the mouth and its diseases", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "music in society, usually non-western music", 
      "illness", 
      "embryos", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins", 
      "the ecology of plant communities", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "the Soviet Union", 
      "everything"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Stomatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rattlesnakes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spiders", 
      "Frogs", 
      "Beetles"
    ], 
    "question": "__________ gather in groups to sleep through the winter. ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "methods", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "dreams", 
      "the therapeutic use of plants", 
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins", 
      "dialects", 
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology", 
      "true bugs", 
      "symptoms"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Methodology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Grist", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Havok", 
      "Dazzle", 
      "Murmur"
    ], 
    "question": "A group of bees can be called either a hive, a swarm, or a __________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "fossil footprints, tracks and burrows", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract", 
      "fermentation", 
      "the structure of diseased tissues", 
      "the practical arts", 
      "mammals", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits", 
      "study of human characteristics", 
      "same as Aetiology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ichnology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hydrogen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oxygen", 
      "Helium", 
      "Carbon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which chemical has the atomic number one?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "ligaments", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "things of which we are by nature ignorant, or of things which cannot be known", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "ants", 
      "men", 
      "sex", 
      "illness", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "geology of celestial bodies"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Desmology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ballistics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kinetics", 
      "Kinesics", 
      "Trajectics"
    ], 
    "question": "Which science deals with the motion of projectiles? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the Sun", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "puzzles", 
      "neural diseases", 
      "prehistoric metaphytes ", 
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "the moon", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "the structure of cells"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Heliology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rubber", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plastic", 
      "Iron", 
      "Wood"
    ], 
    "question": "To What Is The Process Of Vulcanisation Applied?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "waves or wave motions", 
      "eggs", 
      "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Scientology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cats Eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Traffic Light", 
      "Airbag", 
      "Crumple Zone"
    ], 
    "question": "What Road Safety Device Was Invented By Percy Shaw In 1943? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "fossils of ancient life", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the kidneys and their diseases, a branch of medicine", 
      "enzymes", 
      "ants", 
      "measurement", 
      "rocks", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "diseases of stomach and intestines", 
      "the nature and origins of knowledge"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Paleontology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rabbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel", 
      "Pig", 
      "Anteater"
    ], 
    "question": "What animal lives in a warren?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "prehistoric climates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "cancer", 
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being", 
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
      "the structure, function, and pathology of the ear", 
      "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads", 
      "existence", 
      "bones", 
      "heat"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Paleoclimatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Larynx", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Glotula", 
      "Esophagus", 
      "Trachea"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the biological term for the voice box?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "neural diseases", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "rocks", 
      "proper names", 
      "the immune system", 
      "bones"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Neuropathology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Frontal Lobe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cortex", 
      "The Hypothalamus", 
      "The Parietal Lobe"
    ], 
    "question": "What Part Of The Brain Is Affected In A Lobotomy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "interactions among organisms and the water cycle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "the structure of cells", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth", 
      "male health and disease", 
      "existence", 
      "the ecological interrelationships among communities of organisms", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ecohydrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Annual", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Perennial", 
      "Evergreen", 
      "Ephemeral"
    ], 
    "question": "What Name Is Given To A Plant That Grows From Seed & flowers And Dies Within A Year? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "schematic layouts", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "angels", 
      "clouds", 
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes", 
      "existence", 
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Volcanology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Heart", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soul", 
      "Blood"
    ], 
    "question": "Carditis, affects the ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth", 
      "vocal sounds", 
      "feces", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "study of horses", 
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "grasshoppers and crickets", 
      "butterflies and moths"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Homology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tycho Brahe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Johanes Kepler", 
      "Galileo Galilei", 
      "Nicolas Copernicus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which astronomer had a metal nose?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the historical study of languages", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "crop circles", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "the phylum Bryozoa", 
      "a dissimilarity of parts often attributable to a difference in origin", 
      "games and play", 
      "writing systems", 
      "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Philology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lactic acid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Amenic Acid", 
      "Stomach Acid", 
      "Pectic Acid"
    ], 
    "question": "What chemical compound causes pain in muscles after exercise?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "lightning", 
      "measurement", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "wine", 
      "flies", 
      "bones", 
      "sacred texts"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cryology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "206", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "310", 
      "233", 
      "280"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Bones Are There In The Adult Human Body?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "blood", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology", 
      "cancer", 
      "heat", 
      "the fetus, especially when within the uterus", 
      "animal behaviour", 
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes", 
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes", 
      "earthquakes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hematology/Haematology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Opossum", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel", 
      "Coyote", 
      "Otter"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the only native North American marsupial?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "vaccines", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "oceans", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins", 
      "non-terrestrial life", 
      "origin of life", 
      "childbirth, sometimes spelled", 
      "demons", 
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "the internal structures of stars as revealed by their oscillations"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Vaccinology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dolphin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Turtle", 
      "Lion", 
      "Gorilla"
    ], 
    "question": "Apart From Humans There Is Only One Other Creature That Has Sex For Pleasure. What is it? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "underground water", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "Tibet", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "fossil footprints, tracks and burrows", 
      "the hind regions (rectum, anus, colon and pelvic floor) of the body", 
      "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract", 
      "the nature of Buddha", 
      "the relationship of organisms to each other and to their environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hydrogeology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Universe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Milky Way", 
      "Andromeda", 
      "Infinity"
    ], 
    "question": "What was created with the big bang?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "measurement", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations", 
      "spiders and their kind", 
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "the Soviet Union", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "mollusks"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Metrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Transformer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Resister", 
      "Capacitor", 
      "Micrometer"
    ], 
    "question": "What Electrical Device Can Change The Magnitude Of Voltage Or Current", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "children's behavior and development", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "male health and disease", 
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "the anatomy of blood and lymph vascular systems", 
      "the study and analysis of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "clouds", 
      "cats", 
      "everything"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Paedology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Buck", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Doe", 
      "Colt", 
      "A Johnny"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these is a name for a male deer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "glaciers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the atmosphere", 
      "animals", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "fermentation", 
      "sex", 
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Glaciology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Az", 
      "Ri", 
      "Ir"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the symbol for Iron?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study or knowledge of emetics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the mathematical study of closeness and connectedness", 
      "the art and career of using cosmetics to improve beauty", 
      "pollen", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
      "hair and scalp", 
      "ligaments", 
      "disease classification", 
      "China"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Emetology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alchemy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magic", 
      "Aurentalism", 
      "Mystic Metallurgy"
    ], 
    "question": "The ancient attempt to transmute base metals into gold was called ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "China", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fossil footprints, tracks and burrows", 
      "the moon", 
      "everything", 
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures", 
      "museum management", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "snakes", 
      "the Islam"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Sinology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rd", 
      "Gi", 
      "Rm"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for radium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "venereal diseases", 
      "race", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "proper names", 
      "non-terrestrial life", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "dust in the atmosphere and its effects on plants and animals, also spelled 'koniology'"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Graphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Low Blood Pressure", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tight Muscles", 
      "Torn Ligaments", 
      "Weak Tendons"
    ], 
    "question": "What Would You Suffer From With Hypotension?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "museum management", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "parasitic worms", 
      "animal diseases", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment", 
      "prison management and criminal rehabilitation", 
      "ancient multicelled plants", 
      "life in outer space", 
      "musical instruments", 
      "illness"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Museology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Central America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Africa", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Japan"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Is The Natural Habitat Of The Cheese Plant?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "heat", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the future", 
      "the future", 
      "a neologism for the Pilates method, a system of physical exercise", 
      "ants", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "the nature of Buddha", 
      "the functions of the nervous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Thermology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "20 months", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "12 months", 
      "24 months", 
      "16 months"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the gestation period of an Asian Elephant? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "viruses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth", 
      "parasites", 
      "the therapeutic use of plants", 
      "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees", 
      "eggs", 
      "paranormal or psychic phenomenon that defy conventional scientific explanations", 
      "embryos", 
      "microorganisms"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Virology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Albatross", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bald Eagle", 
      "Perigrine Falcon", 
      "Ostrich"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Bird Has The Largest Wingspan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "waves or wave motions", 
      "eggs", 
      "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Scientology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hippopotamus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elephant", 
      "Rhinoceros", 
      "American Bison"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Is The Second Heaviest Land Animal?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a set of words and/or phrases, usually in relation to some particular canon or field of study", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "nematodes", 
      "the nose and its diseases", 
      "parasitic worms", 
      "museum management", 
      "nematodes", 
      "origin of life", 
      "bees", 
      "victims of crime, often applied to characterizing the criminal"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Terminology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mercury", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Zinc", 
      "Cadmium", 
      "Lead"
    ], 
    "question": "What is quicksilver also known as?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "communist Soviet Union", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "ticks and mites", 
      "minerals", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "the study and analysis of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "snakes", 
      "animal behaviour", 
      "insects", 
      "methods"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Sovietology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jurassic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesozoic", 
      "Triassic", 
      "Devonian"
    ], 
    "question": "In Geology What Period followed The Cretaceous?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the ecology of any individual species", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "crayfish", 
      "crayfish", 
      "birds", 
      "lightning", 
      "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics", 
      "wine and winemaking", 
      "the theological study of redemption", 
      "the functions of the nervous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Autecology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Acidity Or Alkalinity", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Radiation", 
      "Wind Speed", 
      "Gravity"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is PH A Measure Of", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the Sun", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "puzzles", 
      "neural diseases", 
      "prehistoric metaphytes ", 
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "the moon", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "the structure of cells"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Heliology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2", 
      "3", 
      "1"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Chambers Are There In Your Heart?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "heat", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the future", 
      "the future", 
      "a neologism for the Pilates method, a system of physical exercise", 
      "ants", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "the nature of Buddha", 
      "the functions of the nervous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Thermology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vacuum", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dark Matter", 
      "Black Hole", 
      "White Hole"
    ], 
    "question": "What term appies to space devoid of matter? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "internal secretory glands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "bees", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "the nature and origins of knowledge", 
      "the Sun", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "a parody of astrology", 
      "society"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Endocrinology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hydroponics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horticulture", 
      "Apedology", 
      "Anapedics"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Method Of Growing Plants Without Soil?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "feces", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "underground water", 
      "the field of medicine that deals with the skin", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "algae", 
      "signs", 
      "signs", 
      "the scientific study of baths, bathing and of their application to disease", 
      "genetic differences in relation to the environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Scatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rabies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Meningitis", 
      "Syphilis", 
      "Alzeimer's"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Hydrophobia Better Known As", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "crop circles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "sex", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "shells and of molluscs", 
      "China", 
      "classification", 
      "lightning"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cereology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stork", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pelican", 
      "Flamingo", 
      "Swan"
    ], 
    "question": "The shoebill __________, native to Africa, is often compared to a statue. The bird will stand perfectly still for long periods waiting for fish to come to surface in the water.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "wood", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "mountains and their mapping", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "men", 
      "eggs", 
      "interactions among organisms and the water cycle"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Xylology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Microwaves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ovens", 
      "Refrigerators", 
      "Dryers"
    ], 
    "question": "Which has longer wavelength?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the relationship of organisms to each other and to their environment", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "bacteria", 
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "the field of dermatological anatomical pathology", 
      "a branch of geology that studies sediments", 
      "race", 
      "cells", 
      "sleep"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Bioecology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Borneo & Sumatra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bali & Lombok", 
      "Sulawesi & Java", 
      "New Guinea & Komodo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which 2 Islands Are The Natural Habitat Of The Orang-Utan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "flow", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the attribute (of a word) of being self descriptive", 
      "medicine relating to women, or of women in general", 
      "the future", 
      "plankton", 
      "illness", 
      "a subsection of anatomy that studies the soft parts", 
      "the biosphere and its relations to the lithosphere and atmosphere", 
      "dietetics"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Rheology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alexander Graham Bell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thomas Edison", 
      "Guglielmo Marconi", 
      "Claude Decibel"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Invented The Telephone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "animals that may or may not be mythical", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "blackberries", 
      "the causes and treatment of allergies; a branch of medicine", 
      "flags", 
      "the art and career of using cosmetics to improve beauty", 
      "stalkers", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
      "old age", 
      "bees"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cryptozoology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "hours", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "days", 
      "minutes", 
      "nights"
    ], 
    "question": "The snail mates only once in its entire life. When it does mate, however, it may take as long as 12 _______ to consummate the act.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "drug dosage", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "origin of life", 
      "diseases of stomach and intestines", 
      "poisons", 
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "symptoms", 
      "prison management and criminal rehabilitation", 
      "rheumatic diseases, a branch of medicine", 
      "bryophytes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Posology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dragon Flies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ants", 
      "Woodlice", 
      "Beetles"
    ], 
    "question": "What Type Of Insects Are Hawkers, Clubtails, Biddies, Emeralds, Darts & Skimmers", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "water", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "human beings killing other human beings", 
      "wonders, or monsters", 
      "heat", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "viruses", 
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "the Soviet Union"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hydrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rabies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Meningitis", 
      "Syphilis", 
      "Alzeimer's"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Hydrophobia Better Known As", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "schematic layouts", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the ecology of plant communities", 
      "in ethics, duty", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "microorganisms", 
      "the writings and practices of historians", 
      "music in society, usually non-western music", 
      "animal behaviour", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Boxology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ear", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nose", 
      "Hand", 
      "Foot"
    ], 
    "question": "Where in the body is the smallest human muscle?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "bryophytes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "life in outer space", 
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "prehistoric climates", 
      "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc", 
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Bryology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hertz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joule", 
      "Pascal", 
      "Newton", 
      "Ohm", 
      "Byte", 
      "Kelvin"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the SI unit for frequency?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "ants", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "the Soviet Union", 
      "prehistoric metazoans ", 
      "the effects of radiation upon living organisms", 
      "the nature of Buddha", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "friction at very small scale", 
      "the signification and application of words"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Myrmecology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Az", 
      "Ri", 
      "Ir"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the symbol for Iron?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "methods", 
      "vocal sounds", 
      "the causes and treatment of allergies; a branch of medicine", 
      "the Shroud of Turin", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "bees", 
      "true bugs", 
      "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Morphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Edward Jenner", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Francis Crick", 
      "Edith Bower", 
      "Marcel Decroix"
    ], 
    "question": "Who developed the vaccine for smallpox?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the liver; a branch of medicine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "the moon", 
      "present-day landforms, traditionally on Earth but with increasing frequency on nearby planetary objects", 
      "the Earth", 
      "study of devil worshipers", 
      "a subsection of anatomy that studies the soft parts", 
      "origin of life", 
      "nerves"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hepatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rabbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel", 
      "Pig", 
      "Anteater"
    ], 
    "question": "What animal lives in a warren?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "karyotypes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "plankton", 
      "the effect of light on chemicals", 
      "paranormal or psychic phenomenon that defy conventional scientific explanations", 
      "methods", 
      "the kidneys and their diseases, a branch of medicine", 
      "flies", 
      "the Sumerians", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Karyology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Americium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Merylium", 
      "Amon", 
      "Amortis"
    ], 
    "question": "What does the symbol 'Am' represent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "syphilis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
      "a dissimilarity of parts often attributable to a difference in origin", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "wine", 
      "the characteristics of the skull", 
      "Semitic cultures", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "interactions among organisms and the water cycle"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Syphilology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Leeches", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vampire Bats", 
      "Cobras", 
      "Wasps"
    ], 
    "question": "What Creatures Were Frequently Used To Bleed Patients In The Nineteeth Century?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "myths", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "mountains and their mapping", 
      "character", 
      "sex", 
      "numbers", 
      "the effect of light on chemicals", 
      "nutrition", 
      "signs", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Mythology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Puffin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Albatross", 
      "Penguin", 
      "Dodo"
    ], 
    "question": "What bird is associated with Lundy Island?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "stalkers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "grasses", 
      "study of human characteristics", 
      "character", 
      "a branch of logic focusing on part-whole relationships", 
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "things of which we are by nature ignorant, or of things which cannot be known", 
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "the nature of values and value judgements"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Beierlology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "8", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2", 
      "4", 
      "10"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Bits In A Byte", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "in ethics, duty", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "a branch of logic focusing on part-whole relationships", 
      "puzzles", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "character"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Laryngology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hydrocarbons", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gases", 
      "Petroleum Spirits", 
      "Methylated Spirits"
    ], 
    "question": "What are Petrol, Naphta, Kerosine, Diesel and Oil?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study or skill of preparing mixed drinks", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "demons", 
      "musical instruments", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "the derivation of a persons character traits, by studying the shape of their skull", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "the Sumerians", 
      "ancient multicelled plants"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Mixology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "9", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1", 
      "40", 
      "28"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the heart rate of the blue whale? (in beats per minute)", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a branch of geology that studies sediments", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "bones", 
      "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract", 
      "the eyes", 
      "ancient multicelled plants", 
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "fungi", 
      "the art and career of using cosmetics to improve beauty"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Sedimentology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Feathers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Bones", 
      "Teeth"
    ], 
    "question": "A robin has nearly 3,000 __________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "prehistoric metazoans ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations", 
      "planets and solar systems; more commonly called Planetary science", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "religion"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Paleozoology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Milky way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Andromedu", 
      "Ursa", 
      "Orion"
    ], 
    "question": "Our galaxy is commonly known called _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "snakes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "disease classification", 
      "prehistoric metaphytes ", 
      "society", 
      "flies", 
      "human beings killing other human beings", 
      "diseases of stomach and intestines", 
      "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc", 
      "museum management"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Serpentology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Microwaves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ovens", 
      "Refrigerators", 
      "Dryers"
    ], 
    "question": "Which has longer wavelength?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "life in outer space", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "prehistoric people and human origins", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology", 
      "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
      "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Exobiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Es", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "El", 
      "En", 
      "Ei"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for einsteinium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "grasses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being", 
      "clouds", 
      "dietetics", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "ants", 
      "ancient multicelled plants", 
      "the study, especially statistical, of elections", 
      "the internal structures of stars as revealed by their oscillations"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Agrostology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Hudson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Isambard Kingdom Brunel", 
      "Robert Stephenson", 
      "Thomas Telford"
    ], 
    "question": "In The 19th Century Who Was The Railway King?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "insects", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "earthquakes", 
      "past cultures through the analysis of material remains", 
      "the study and the art of bell ringing", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "study of horses"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Entomology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cirrhosis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hepatitis", 
      "Scurvy", 
      "Meningitis"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Disease Of The Liver Is Associated With Alcoholism?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures", 
      "the characteristics of the skull", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "vocal sounds", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "shells and of molluscs"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Edaphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iodine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Potassium", 
      "Chlorine", 
      "Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "What element is lacking in a diet when goitre occurs?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the effects of radiation upon living organisms", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fossils of ancient life", 
      "the art and career of using cosmetics to improve beauty", 
      "though not an -ology, is a commemoration of a person's life at his/her funeral", 
      "underground water", 
      "internal secretory glands", 
      "flow", 
      "ticks and mites"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Actinobiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Birdilia", 
      "Flowana", 
      "Aerilys"
    ], 
    "question": "In the animal kingdom, if reptiles are in class reptilia, then birds are in class ____?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "algae", 
      "karyotypes", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "the Earth", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "mental processes in living creatures", 
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Anesthesiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Incisors", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Molars", 
      "Premolars", 
      "Slicers"
    ], 
    "question": "The teeth used for biting or cutting are known as _______.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "feces", 
      "study of the mouth and its diseases", 
      "karyotypes", 
      "the process of biological evolution", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "the climate", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Reflexology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sclera", 
      "Cornea", 
      "Retina"
    ], 
    "question": "Which membrane controls the amount of light entering the eye?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the physiological bases of psychological processes", 
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "proper names", 
      "the purported influences of celestial bodies on earthly affairs", 
      "the Soviet Union", 
      "oceans", 
      "past cultures through the analysis of material remains", 
      "human beings killing other human beings"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Indology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Flea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tick", 
      "Rat", 
      "Dust Mite"
    ], 
    "question": "What type of animal is pulex irritants?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "water", 
      "the nature and origins of knowledge", 
      "microorganisms", 
      "nutrition", 
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "earthquakes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Codicology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "J Robert Oppenheimer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Albert Einstein", 
      "Richard Feynman", 
      "Niels Bohr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Director Of The Atomic Lab At Los Alamos New Mexico?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment", 
      "methods", 
      "hair and scalp", 
      "the study and interpretation of symbols, or a set of symbols", 
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "the biosphere and its relations to the lithosphere and atmosphere", 
      "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Odontology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "J Robert Oppenheimer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Albert Einstein", 
      "Richard Feynman", 
      "Niels Bohr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Director Of The Atomic Lab At Los Alamos New Mexico?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the Sun", 
      "music in society, usually non-western music", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "the ear and throat; a branch of medicine", 
      "mental processes in living creatures", 
      "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ecogeomorphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Wind", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Solar", 
      "Tidal", 
      "Nuclear"
    ], 
    "question": "What energy does an Eolic power station generate?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "blackberries", 
      "grasses", 
      "pollen", 
      "bacteria", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "karyotypes", 
      "everything", 
      "hearing; a branch of medicine"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hieroglyphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tongue", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "platysma", 
      "buccinator", 
      "epicranius"
    ], 
    "question": "What muscle is joined by the lingual nerve to the brain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "bacteria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "vibrations and oscillations in the Sun", 
      "present-day landforms, traditionally on Earth but with increasing frequency on nearby planetary objects", 
      "the physiological bases of psychological processes", 
      "the structure of diseased tissues", 
      "a discipline that attempts to reconstruct the transmission of a text on the basis of relations between the various surviving manuscripts", 
      "Mars", 
      "the ancient Egyptians", 
      "the ecology of plant communities"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Bacteriology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Poisons", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Radiation", 
      "Abstract Categorisation", 
      "Venomous Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Toxicology The Study Of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "periodic biological phenomena such as flowering, migration, breeding, etc", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "non-terrestrial life", 
      "religion", 
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "prehistoric life", 
      "the study and analysis of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "study of refuse and trash", 
      "rocks"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phenology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Red", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Purple", 
      "Yellow", 
      "Blue"
    ], 
    "question": "What Colour Does Litmus Paper Turn When Dipped In Acid?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "religion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "measurement", 
      "children's behavior and development", 
      "blood serum", 
      "everything", 
      "a synonym of Pulmonology", 
      "life in outer space", 
      "old age", 
      "reptiles and amphibians"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Theology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hydrogen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oxygen", 
      "Helium", 
      "Carbon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which chemical has the atomic number one?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the ancient Egyptians", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "shells and of molluscs", 
      "the kidneys and their diseases, a branch of medicine", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "old age", 
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "the study or skill of preparing mixed drinks", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Egyptology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sulfuric acid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salt", 
      "Water", 
      "Coal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which substance has the chemical formula H2SO4?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "prehistoric metazoans ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations", 
      "planets and solar systems; more commonly called Planetary science", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "religion"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Paleozoology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rat", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel", 
      "Rabbit", 
      "Shrew"
    ], 
    "question": "A __________ can squeeze through an opening no larger than a dime?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the writings and practices of historians", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the practical arts", 
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "ligaments", 
      "a discipline that attempts to reconstruct the transmission of a text on the basis of relations between the various surviving manuscripts", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "the relationship of organisms to each other and to their environment", 
      "humans"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Historiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sulfuric acid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salt", 
      "Water", 
      "Coal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which substance has the chemical formula H2SO4?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the fetus, especially when within the uterus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the future", 
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "crime", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "the study, especially statistical, of elections", 
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Fetology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Talus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tibia", 
      "Fibia", 
      "Metatarsal"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the second largest bone in the foot?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the moon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a synonym for taxonomy", 
      "heat", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "reptiles and amphibians", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "sleep"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Selenology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Puffin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Albatross", 
      "Penguin", 
      "Dodo"
    ], 
    "question": "What bird is associated with Lundy Island?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "genetic differences in relation to the environment", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a discipline that attempts to reconstruct the transmission of a text on the basis of relations between the various surviving manuscripts", 
      "study of devil worshipers", 
      "human growth", 
      "the study or knowledge of emetics", 
      "bacteria", 
      "non-terrestrial life", 
      "rheumatic diseases, a branch of medicine", 
      "venereal diseases"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Genecology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Earwig", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ant", 
      "Praying Mantis", 
      "Woodlouse"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Insect Has A Pair Of Prominent Pincers At The Tip Of It's Abdomen?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study or skill of preparing mixed drinks", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "demons", 
      "musical instruments", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "the derivation of a persons character traits, by studying the shape of their skull", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "the Sumerians", 
      "ancient multicelled plants"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Mixology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Computer Mouse", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Electric Watch", 
      "Fingerprint scanner", 
      "Microwave"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Gadget Was Invented By Douglas Englebart In 1964", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "reptiles and amphibians", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Semitic cultures", 
      "the therapeutic use of plants", 
      "dragonflies and damselflies", 
      "a dissimilarity of parts often attributable to a difference in origin", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "fungi", 
      "algae", 
      "friction at very small scale"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Herpetology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rubber", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plastic", 
      "Iron", 
      "Wood"
    ], 
    "question": "To What Is The Process Of Vulcanisation Applied?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "lightning", 
      "measurement", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "wine", 
      "flies", 
      "bones", 
      "sacred texts"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cryology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "To Get Insects Below The Bark", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "To attract a mate", 
      "To communicate", 
      "To make a nest"
    ], 
    "question": "Why Does The Woodpecker Peck Wood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the signification and application of words", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "crayfish", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "poisons", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment", 
      "the physiological bases of psychological processes", 
      "the phylum Bryozoa", 
      "fermentation"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Lexicology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Heart", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soul", 
      "Blood"
    ], 
    "question": "Carditis, affects the ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the structure of cells", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "study of human characteristics", 
      "feces", 
      "the study or knowledge of emetics", 
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "hearing; a branch of medicine", 
      "symptoms", 
      "the attribute (of a word) of being self descriptive"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cytomorphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crocodile", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kangaroo", 
      "Cow", 
      "Goliath Spider"
    ], 
    "question": "The __________ does not chew its food, but swallows it whole.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the structure of diseased tissues", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the biosphere and its relations to the lithosphere and atmosphere", 
      "the liver; a branch of medicine", 
      "study of horses", 
      "parasites", 
      "heat", 
      "measurement", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "dogs"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Histopathology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Red", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Purple", 
      "Yellow", 
      "Blue"
    ], 
    "question": "What Colour Does Litmus Paper Turn When Dipped In Acid?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the ecology of any individual species", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "crayfish", 
      "crayfish", 
      "birds", 
      "lightning", 
      "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics", 
      "wine and winemaking", 
      "the theological study of redemption", 
      "the functions of the nervous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Autecology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Antelope", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bison", 
      "Elk", 
      "Deer"
    ], 
    "question": "What large herbivore sleeps only one hour a night?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "dust in the atmosphere and its effects on plants and animals, also spelled 'koniology'", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "life", 
      "sometimes spelled idealogy, is a system of ideas about politics, human life or culture", 
      "dogs", 
      "though not an -ology, is a commemoration of a person's life at his/her funeral", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "rocks", 
      "stalkers", 
      "society"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Coniology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "206", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "310", 
      "233", 
      "280"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Bones Are There In The Adult Human Body?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "humans", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the medical study of the causation of disease", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc", 
      "dogs", 
      "war in an interdisciplinary context", 
      "primates", 
      "heat", 
      "heat"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Anthropology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Plankton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fishes", 
      "Algae", 
      "Larvae"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the name of the minute organisms found drifting near the surface of seas and lakes? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the Sumerians", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals that may or may not be mythical", 
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "fish", 
      "music in society, usually non-western music", 
      "crop circles", 
      "study of refuse and trash", 
      "earthquakes", 
      "butterflies and moths"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Sumerology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mangrove", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wetlands", 
      "Marsh", 
      "Everglades"
    ], 
    "question": "Dense seawater swamps along coasts of hot countries are called ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "medicine relating to women, or of women in general", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "prehistoric climates", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology", 
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "sometimes spelled idealogy, is a system of ideas about politics, human life or culture", 
      "insects", 
      "mollusks"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Gynaecology or Gynecology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shark", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Whale", 
      "Dolphin", 
      "Orca"
    ], 
    "question": "The fins of what sea creature are made into a soup?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "mollusks", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the Earth", 
      "dialects", 
      "religion", 
      "the ecology of any individual species", 
      "the effect of light on chemicals", 
      "humans", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
      "proper names"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Malacology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rabbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel", 
      "Pig", 
      "Anteater"
    ], 
    "question": "What animal lives in a warren?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "bryophytes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "life in outer space", 
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "prehistoric climates", 
      "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc", 
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Bryology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Seven", 
      "Six", 
      "Eight"
    ], 
    "question": "How many planets are there in our solar system?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "victims of crime, often applied to characterizing the criminal", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "embryos", 
      "the anatomy of blood and lymph vascular systems", 
      "study of the mouth and its diseases", 
      "movement in relation to human anatomy; a branch of medicine", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "the eyes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Victimology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What color spots has the common ladybird?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the moon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a synonym for taxonomy", 
      "heat", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "reptiles and amphibians", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "sleep"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Selenology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catalyst", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Precursor", 
      "Solvent", 
      "Base"
    ], 
    "question": "In dyeing what is the name given to the substance used for fixing the colour?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the physiological bases of psychological processes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the functions of the nervous system", 
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract", 
      "the Sun", 
      "flow", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins", 
      "pollen", 
      "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads", 
      "old age"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Psychophysiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Centipedes And Millipedes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Crabs and Lobsters", 
      "Slugs and Snails", 
      "Scorpions and Spiders"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these pairs are Myriapods?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "ticks and mites", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "study of the mouth and its diseases", 
      "the art and career of using cosmetics to improve beauty", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "the heart", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Acarology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Virtual Reality", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Augmented Reality", 
      "Visual Hologram", 
      "Immersive Space"
    ], 
    "question": "What 2 Word Term Is Given To A Simulated 3D Environment Used in Computer Graphics? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study and the art of bell ringing", 
      "the physiological bases of psychological processes", 
      "the theological study of redemption", 
      "clouds", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "flow", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "fungi"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ecophysiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Microwaves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ovens", 
      "Refrigerators", 
      "Dryers"
    ], 
    "question": "Which has longer wavelength?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "existence", 
      "dreams", 
      "the study or knowledge of emetics", 
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "flow", 
      "geology of celestial bodies", 
      "venereal diseases", 
      "geology of celestial bodies"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Agrobiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What color spots has the common ladybird?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "karyotypes", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "plants; botany", 
      "mollusks", 
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "the nature of Buddha", 
      "human beings killing other human beings", 
      "the structure, function, and pathology of the ear"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Traumatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cloud", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Planet", 
      "Island", 
      "Volcano"
    ], 
    "question": "Cirrus and Cumulus are types of what?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "living tissues", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "angels", 
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the historical study of languages", 
      "male health and disease", 
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "the study of picture postcards"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Histology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "8", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2", 
      "4", 
      "10"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Bits In A Byte", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "drug dosage", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "origin of life", 
      "diseases of stomach and intestines", 
      "poisons", 
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "symptoms", 
      "prison management and criminal rehabilitation", 
      "rheumatic diseases, a branch of medicine", 
      "bryophytes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Posology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Philips", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Panasonic", 
      "Viewsonic", 
      "Sony"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Dutch Company Began Marketing Compact Disc Players In 1982?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "games and play", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "blood serum", 
      "the scientific study of baths, bathing and of their application to disease", 
      "word origins", 
      "grasses", 
      "a synonym for taxonomy", 
      "wood", 
      "classification", 
      "music"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ludology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rubber", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plastic", 
      "Iron", 
      "Wood"
    ], 
    "question": "To What Is The Process Of Vulcanisation Applied?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "internal secretory glands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "bees", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "the nature and origins of knowledge", 
      "the Sun", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "a parody of astrology", 
      "society"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Endocrinology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Monkey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Bird", 
      "A Rodent", 
      "A Marsupial"
    ], 
    "question": "What Kind Of Animal Is A Marmoset?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the Shroud of Turin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the functions of the nervous system", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "the future", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "neural diseases", 
      "clouds", 
      "old age"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Sindonology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dolphin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Turtle", 
      "Lion", 
      "Gorilla"
    ], 
    "question": "Apart From Humans There Is Only One Other Creature That Has Sex For Pleasure. What is it? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the heart", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "past cultures through the analysis of material remains", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "ends or final causes", 
      "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees", 
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "children's behavior and development", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "friction at very small scale"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cardiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Smallpox", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Infuenza", 
      "COVID-19", 
      "Rubella"
    ], 
    "question": "What Vaccine Did Edward Jenner Develop? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "wonders, or monsters", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "myths", 
      "fungi", 
      "karyotypes", 
      "the derivation of a persons character traits, by studying the shape of their skull", 
      "the process of biological evolution", 
      "cancer", 
      "karyotypes", 
      "the ear and throat; a branch of medicine"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Teratology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blue", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yellow", 
      "Purple", 
      "Red"
    ], 
    "question": "What Colour Is Sonic the Hedgehog?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "race", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "parasites", 
      "in ethics, duty", 
      "rocks", 
      "grasses", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "though not an -ology, is a commemoration of a person's life at his/her funeral", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "the functions of the nervous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ethnology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jurassic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesozoic", 
      "Triassic", 
      "Devonian"
    ], 
    "question": "In Geology What Period followed The Cretaceous?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "waves or wave motions", 
      "eggs", 
      "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Scientology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2", 
      "3", 
      "1"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Chambers Are There In Your Heart?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the lymph system and glands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "measurement", 
      "human beings killing other human beings", 
      "grasses", 
      "feces", 
      "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system", 
      "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics", 
      "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc", 
      "prehistoric metaphytes "
    ], 
    "question": "What is Lymphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dragon Flies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ants", 
      "Woodlice", 
      "Beetles"
    ], 
    "question": "What Type Of Insects Are Hawkers, Clubtails, Biddies, Emeralds, Darts & Skimmers", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a branch of logic focusing on part-whole relationships", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "karyotypes", 
      "drugs", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "ants", 
      "the mathematical study of closeness and connectedness", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "drugs", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Mereology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Flea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tick", 
      "Rat", 
      "Dust Mite"
    ], 
    "question": "What type of animal is pulex irritants?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "cells", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "genetic differences in relation to the environment", 
      "war in an interdisciplinary context", 
      "hair and scalp", 
      "lightning", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "the study and design of machines at the molecular level"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cytology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Electroconvulsive Therapy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Endrine Cardio Therapy", 
      "Endless Carotid Tears", 
      "Environmental Combined Theatre"
    ], 
    "question": "What Does E C T Stand For", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "weather", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animal diseases", 
      "hair and scalp", 
      "human beings killing other human beings", 
      "physical, psychological and social problems associated with dying", 
      "the ear and throat; a branch of medicine", 
      "crop circles", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "wine and winemaking"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Meteorology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dynamite", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The combustion engine", 
      "Plastic", 
      "The printing press"
    ], 
    "question": "What Did Alfred Nobel Invent Before Initiating His Nobel Peace Prize Award Scheme?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "men", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "stalkers", 
      "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
      "fish", 
      "the study and interpretation of symbols, or a set of symbols", 
      "weather", 
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "a parody of astrology", 
      "dogs"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dudology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ecdysis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Descaling", 
      "Poreolasis", 
      "Unsheathing"
    ], 
    "question": "The process of a snake shedding its skin or a crustacean casting off its outer shell is called __________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the historical study of languages", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "crop circles", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "the phylum Bryozoa", 
      "a dissimilarity of parts often attributable to a difference in origin", 
      "games and play", 
      "writing systems", 
      "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Philology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rabies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Meningitis", 
      "Syphilis", 
      "Alzeimer's"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Hydrophobia Better Known As", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the historical study of languages", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "crop circles", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "the phylum Bryozoa", 
      "a dissimilarity of parts often attributable to a difference in origin", 
      "games and play", 
      "writing systems", 
      "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Philology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Es", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "El", 
      "En", 
      "Ei"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for einsteinium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }
]
